

Hojjatollah Sadeqi sadeqi@yazd.ac.ir https://www.yazd. ac.ir/eng/sadeqi (+98) 912-4946469

Address Dianat Street Yazd, Razmandegan Iran

Hojjatollah Sadeqi

Assistant Professor

About Me After receiving my PhD in Public Administration, teaching as Assistant Professor at Yazd University for six years, and working as a member of Yazd Research and Technology Fund Board of Directors, I am working on Risk Manegement and Financial Data Mining. I have also worked as a consultant for several theses and dissertations on Finance and Management at the university.

Education

2005 - 2010, Allame Tabatabee University, Tehran

PhD in Public Administration (Comparative and Development Management)

1999 - 2005, Imam Sadiq University, Tehran

MS in Finance

Experience

March 2010 - present, Assistant Professor of Finance, Yazd University

May 2016 - present, Deputy of Economics, Management and Accounting School, Yazd University

February 2017 - present, Researcher, Center for Science and Technology Research, Yazd University

July 2015 - July 2017, Member of Board of Directors, Yazd Research and Technology Fund

February 2015 - May 2016, Dean of Accounting Department, Yazd University

September 2012 - September 2014, Dean of Business Management Department, Yazd University

October 2013 - October 2014, Member of Entrepreneurship Committee, Yazd University

Teaching Experience

2016-2018, Yazd University

Research Method in Accounting, Risk Management, Investment Management, Financial Engineering

2015, Yazd University

Research Method in Finance, Advaced Financial Engineering, Case Studies in Finance

2010-2015, Yazd University

Business Research Methods, Organization Theories, Financial Mathematics, Investment Management, Financial Engineering

Language

IELTS

Overall Band score: 6.50



Hojjatollah Sadeqi sadeqi@yazd.ac.ir https://www.yazd. ac.ir/eng/sadeqi (+98) 912-4946469

Address Dianat Street Yazd, Razmandegan Iran

Software Development Skills

Programming
R and Matlab
Computer Software
SPSS and Atlas.ti

Interests

Professional

Risk Management, Financial Engineering, Credit Risk , Financial Management, Software Design